HERE Communications Department Photographs 6199/005 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
HERE Communications Department Photographs
1911-2003
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union (HERE)
6199/005 P
34.56 cubic feet
34.6 linear ft.
Photographs.
7626649
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, April 12, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 27, 2015
Biographical / Historical
The Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees Union (HERE), was a labor union for workers in the hospitality industry and was formed in 1891. HERE merged with the Union of Neddletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE), in 2004, to form UNITE HERE.
HERE and later UNITE HERE were affiliated with the AFL-CIO until September of 2005, when the General Executive Board of UNITE HERE voted to leave the AFL-CIO and join in with the Change to Win Coalition.
Scope and Contents
This collection has over twenty four thousand photographs, over sixteen hundred slides, and various other media containing photographs, used to document the Locals that belong to HERE. Captured on film are meetings, conferences, award ceremonies and many other events.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6199/005: HERE Communications Department Files
Hotels -- Employees -- Labor unions -- United States; Restaurants -- Employees -- Labor unions -- United States; Hospitality industry -- Employees -- Labor unions -- United States; Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union; Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union -- Photographs; Hotel, Hospital, Restaurant, and Tavern Employees' Union --Photographs
7626649
- AFL-CIO Board Meeting (Box 1, Folder 1)
- AFL-CIO Conference - AIDS (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Scope and Contents
  3 photographs
- Merger - AFL-CIO (1955) Convention - NY Dec. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  24 photographs
- Convention - AF-CIO -- 1957 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  16 photographs
- AFL-CIO Convention (CIE-Jan. 1958) -- 1957 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  8 photographs
- AFL-CIO -- 1959 Convention (Box 1, Folder 6)
  47 photographs
- AFL-CIO - 1961 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  41 photographs
- AFL-CIO Convention - 1968 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  1 photograph
- AFL-CIO Convention (Box 1, Folder 9)
  6 photographs
- AFL-CIO Convention - 1973 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  2 photographs
- AFL-CIO Economy Conference - Feb. 1975 in Washington, DC (Box 1, Folder 11)
  7 photographs
- AFL-CIO Convention - 1976 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  13 photographs
- AFL-CIO Convention 1981 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  22 photographs
- AFL-CIO Executive Council Meeting - February 1990 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- AFL-CIO Organizing Conference - August 1997 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  9 photographs
- AFL-CIO Convention - Pittsburgh - September 1997 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  52 photographs - photograph proof sheets
- AFL-CIO Conventions (Box 1, Folder 17)
  14 photographs
- AFL-CIO - Misc. (Box 1, Folder 18)
- AFL-CIO Show (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Africa and Asia (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Airlift -- 1978 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  10 photographs; proof sheets
- APALA [Asian Pacific American Labor Alliance] (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Aramark Workers (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Auditors (Box 1, Folder 24)
  9 photographs, negatives
- Auditors (Box 1, Folder 25)
  18 photographs
- Auditors Report Photos Spring 1996 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Auditing Committee (Box 1, Folder 27)
  21 photographs
- Auditing Committee (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Auditing Committee - July 1960 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  2 Photographs
- Auditing Committee -- 1962 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  1 photographs
- Auditing Committee -- 1965 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  39 photographs
- Auditing Committee -- 1968 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Auditing Committee -- 1969 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  5 photographs
- Int. auditing Committee (see June 1970 CIE) (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Auditing Committee -- 1972 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Int. Auditing Committee -- 1973 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  4 photographs
- Int. Auditing Committee -- 1974 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Int. Auditing Committee -- 1976 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Audit Committee? -- March 1992 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Auditors training (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Australian visitor -- March 30, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Austrian visitor (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Awards, Banners, Ribbons (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Award ceremonies (Box 1, Folder 44)
  11 photographs
- Barney's Birthday. Staff Shots -- 11/3/1989 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  19 photographs
- Baseball game (Box 1, Folder 46)
  23 photographs
- Bedroom (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Benefits (Applying for them) (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Board -- 1984 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  68 photographs
- Board Meeting - 1973 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Board Meeting - 1983 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  79 photographs
- Butcher (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Canadian Regional Office (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Capitol Building (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Celebration (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Celebration (Box 1, Folder 56)
  10 photographs
- Celebration (Box 1, Folder 57)
  27 photographs
- Celebrations (Box 1, Folder 58)
  60 photographs
- Celebrations, Awards (Box 1, Folder 59)
  78 photographs
- Celebrations - Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 60)
- Childcare (Box 1, Folder 61)
- Child labor (Box 1, Folder 62)
- Children (Box 1, Folder 63)
- Christmas (Box 1, Folder 64)
  20 photographs
- CIE (Box 1, Folder 65)
- CIE - 1931-1941 (Box 1, Folder 66)
- CIE - 1947 (Box 1, Folder 67)
- CIE - 1969 (Box 1, Folder 68)
- CIE - 1974 (Box 1, Folder 69)
- CIE - 1976 (Box 1, Folder 70)
- CIE - 1977 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  32 photographs; proof sheets
- CIE - 1978 (Box 1, Folder 72)
- CIE - 1979 (Box 1, Folder 73)
- CIE-1981 (Box 1, Folder 74)
- CIE - 1982 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  31 photographs
- CIE - 1982 (Box 1, Folder 76)
- CIE - July/August 1982 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  30 photographs
- CIE - 1983 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  25 photographs
- CIE - June 1984 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- CIE - September/October 1984 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- CIE - December 1984 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- CIT - 1985 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  15 photographs
- CIE - April 1986 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- CIE - 1987 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  17 photographs
- CIE - 1988 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- CIE - 1990 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  1 cartoon
- January 1991 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  35 photographs
- CIE - February 1991 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  3 news paper pictures
- CIT - April 1991 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- CIE - August/September 1991 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  44 photographs
- CIE - November/December 1991 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- CIE - Issues photos 1992 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- November/December 1992 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- CIE - January/February 1993 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- March/April 1993 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- CIE - May/June 1993 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- CIE - July/August 1993 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- September/October 1993 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- CIE - November/December 1993 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  42 photographs
- January/February 1994 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  13 Photographs
- March/April 1994 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- May/June 1994 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- July/August 1994 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- September/October 1994 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- November/December 1994 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- January/February 1995 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- CIE - March/April 1995 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- May/June 1995 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- May/June 1995 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- July/August 1995 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- September/October 1995 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- CIE - November/December 1995 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- CIE - March/April 1996 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- CIE - July/august 1996 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- CIE - September/October 1996 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- CIE - September/October 1996 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  85 CIE - January/February 1997
- CIE - January/February 1997 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- CIE - March/April 1997 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- May/June 1997 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- CIE - July/August 1997 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- CIE - September/October 1997 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- CIE - January/February 1998 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  12 photographs; 3 slides
- CIE - Year unknown (Box 3, Folder 2)
  58 photographs; 1 floppy disc; negative sheets
- CIE - Year unknown (Box 3, Folder 3)
  54 photographs
- CIE - March/April (Box 3, Folder 4)
- CIE - Covers (Box 3, Folder 5)
  26 photographs
- CIE Covers (Box 3, Folder 6)
- CIE - Cover (Box 3, Folder 7)
- CIE - Frontier Strike (Box 3, Folder 8)
  18 photographs; 1 floppy disc
- CIE - Issue Meeting (Box 3, Folder 9)
- CIE - Miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 10)
- CIE - Miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 11)
  38 photographs
- Cincinnati Office 1976 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Cincinnati Offices (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Cincinnati Office (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Negs for photos taken in Cincinnati Office -- April 1957 - CIE (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Class (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Clinton Campaign Summer 1992 (negs) (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Computers (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Conference (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Conference (Box 3, Folder 20)
  33 photographs
- Conference (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Conference (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Conference (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Conference (Box 3, Folder 24)
  46 photographs
- Conference (Box 3, Folder 25)
  200 photographs
- Conference (Box 3, Folder 26)
  43 photographs
- Conference (Box 3, Folder 27)
  36 photographs
- Conference -- 1973? (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Associate member Conference -- 1989 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- IUF Conference - DC -- 1992 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- I.L.O. Conference (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Legislative Conference - March 4-7, 1974 (Washington, D.C.) (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Conference Misc. (Box 3, Folder 33)
  45 photographs
- Conference - Miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Conference - the New Frontier (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Organizing Campaign Conference 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  66 photographs
- Organizing SWAT Team conference -- Oct. 1987 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Washington, D.C. -- Leg Conference, May 2000 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  76 photographs
- Contract Signings (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Convention (Box 3, Folder 40)
  275 photographs
- Convention (Box 3, Folder 41)
- Convention (Box 3, Folder 42)
  131 photographs
- Convention (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Convention (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Convention (Box 4, Folder 3)
  80 photographs
- Conventions (Box 4, Folder 4)
  87 photographs
- Conventions (Box 4, Folder 5)
  154 photographs
- Conventions (Box 4, Folder 6)
  34 photographs
- Convention, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Convention, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  88 photographs
- Convention, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  negative sheets, 48 photographs
- Convention, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Convention, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  negative sheets, proof sheets
- Convention, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  93 photographs
- Convention, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Convention, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Convention, Aug. 1976, Palms Springs, California (Box 4, Folder 15)
  178 photographs
- HERE 1976 Convention (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Convention, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Convention, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Convention, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  10 photographs, 3 slides
- Convention - 1983 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  28 photographs
- Convention, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  107 photographs
- Convention, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  201 photographs
- Convention, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  173 photographs
- Convention (Box 4, Folder 24)
  190 photographs
- Convention 1985 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  171 photographs
- Convention, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  56 photographs
- Convention, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  143 photographs
- Convention, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- 37th General Convention (Box 5, Folder 2)
- 1991 Convention (Box 5, Folder 3)
- 1991 Convention (Box 5, Folder 4)
  151 photographs
- 1991 Convention (Box 5, Folder 5)
  157 photographs
- 1991 Convention (Box 5, Folder 6)
  148 photographs
- HERE Convention 1991 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  Proof sheets
- HERE Convention 1991 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  Proof Sheets, 11 photographs
- Convention, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  Proof sheets, 1 photograph
- HERE Convention (Box 5, Folder 10)
  20 slides
- 41st General Convention (Box 5, Folder 11)
- 42nd General Convention, Chicago 7/96, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Convention, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- 43rd General Convention (Box 5, Folder 14)
  231 photographs
- Convention - 43rd General (Box 5, Folder 15)
  208 photographs
- 43rd General Convention (Box 5, Folder 16)
  199 photographs
- Convention 1999 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Convention 2001 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  65 photographs
- Convention 2001 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  1 floppy disc; 36 photographs
- America needs a raise (Convention) (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Chicago Convention (Box 5, Folder 21)
  12 photographs
- HERE and BIU convention 1971, Chicago, Ill. (Box 5, Folder 22)
  78 photographs; negatives
- Chicago Convention 1971 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  81 photographs; proof sheets
- Chicago Convention 1981 (includes office staff of Cincinnati and Washington, DC offices and Auditing Councils) (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Convention Center, New Orleans (Box 6, Folder 1)
- I.L.P.A. 1959 Convention (Box 6, Folder 2)
- I.L.P.A. 1960 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- I.L..A. 1961 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- I.L.P.A. 1968 Convention (Box 6, Folder 5)
- I.L.P.A. 1969 Convention (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Conventions - Miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 7)
  71 photographs
- Conventions - Miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Conventions - Miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Culinary Arts Show - 1961 Convention - Philadelphia (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Convention - Philadelphia 1961 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Convention - Philadelphia 1961 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Convention - Philadelphia - 1961 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Convention - San Diego - 1955 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Special Convention - 1958 - Cleveland, OH (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Special Convention - San Francisco, CA 1974 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Special Convention - San Francisco, CA 1974 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  83 photographs
- Convention - Special Pictures -- 1974 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Diamond Jubilee Convention - St. Louis, MO. -- May 1966 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- I.U.F. NARO DC Convention -- 1989 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  52 phonographs
- Cook of the month (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Corcoran School (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Corcoran School (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Corcoran School (Box 6, Folder 24)
  2 photographs; proof sheet
- Corcoran School (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Corcoran School (Box 6, Folder 26)
  128 photographs
- Corcoran School (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Corcoran School exterior shots (Box 6, Folder 28)
  5 photographs; 5 slides
- Corcoran School - Offices after renovation (Box 6, Folder 29)
  172 photographs
- Culinary Institute of America. New Haven, Conn. (Box 6, Folder 30)
- CULLS 11/5/1999 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  67 photographs
- Dinner (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Charles Gand's Dinner (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Joint Board Dinner -- New York 12/9/1955 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Pat Gorman Dinner (Box 6, Folder 35)
- St. Jude Dinner (Box 6, Folder 36)
  42 photographs; proof sheets
- Testimonial Dinner - 1955 -- Miller (Box 6, Folder 37)
- Dunlop Commission (Box 6, Folder 38)
- Education (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Egyptian Visitors -- June 1990 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  40 photographs
- El Borracho (former #45 members) (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Elderly (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Executive Board -- 1991 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Executive Board, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Executive Council, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Executive Board Meetings (Box 7, Folder 8)
  12 slides; negatives; proof sheets; 10 photographs
- Food and Beverage Trades (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Fun Afield (the "Fish" File) (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Gaining Commission - Atlantic city - January 1998 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- General Board of Directors Meeting - January 1990 -- Hawaii Conference (Box 7, Folder 12)
  163 photographs
- General Board of Directors Meeting. January 1990 -- Hawaii Conference (Box 7, Folder 13)
  74 photographs
- General Executive Board (Box 7, Folder 14)
- GEB Meeting (Box 7, Folder 15)
- GEB August 3 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- G.E.B. 1996 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  29 slides
- G.E.B. 1986 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  7 slides; 7 photographs
- HEREIU GEB Meeting - Chicago -- June 1997 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- HERE IU GEB Meeting -- Chicago -- June 1997 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  negatives; 44 photographs
- Board meeting - Chicago - Summer 1998 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- G.E.B. Meeting - November 26, 1973 -- Honolulu, Hawaii (Box 7, Folder 22)
- G.E.B. Meeting - Las Vegas - January 1961 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  70 photographs
- GEB Meeting - Las Vegas - January 1961 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  39 photographs; negatives
- G.E.B. 1970 -- Las Vegas (Box 7, Folder 25)
  99 photographs; proof sheets
- G.E.B. 1970 - Las Vegas (Box 7, Folder 26)
  59 photographs; proof sheets
- Las Vegas GEB Meeting - March 1999 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  146 photographs
- G.E.B. Meeting - March 1960 -- Los Angeles (Box 7, Folder 28)
- G.E.B. Meeting 1962 -- Miami Beach (Box 7, Folder 29)
- G.E.B. Meeting - 1971 - Miami Beach, FL (Box 7, Folder 30)
- G.E.B. Meeting - Miami Beach, GL -- 1973 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- G.E.B. -- Miami Beach -- 1974 (Box 7, Folder 32)
- G.E.B. Meeting -- Minneapolis, Minn. June 11-16, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 33)
- G.E.B. Meeting - Palm Springs -- 1975 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  3 photographs; proof sheets
- G.E.B. Meeting -- Palm Springs, CA 1975 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  Proof sheets; 51 photographs
- G.E.B. Meeting -- Palm Springs, CA 1975 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  63 photographs
- G.E.B. Meeting -- Palm Springs, February 1976 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- G.E.B. Meeting - January 1978 - Palm Springs (Box 8, Folder 2)
  24 photographs; proof sheets; negatives
- G.E.B. Meeting - Palm Springs, CA, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  97 photographs; negatives
- G.E.B. Meeting - 1983 - Palm Springs (Box 8, Folder 4)
- G.E.B. Meeting - (College of the Desert) Palm Springs - 1986 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  217 photographs
- G.E.B. Meeting. (College of the Desert) Palm Springs 1986 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  Negatives; 5 slides
- G.E.B. 1988 Marquis Hotel - Palm Springs (Box 8, Folder 7)
  287 photographs
- G.E.B. Meeting - 1988 - Marquis Hotel - Palm Springs (Box 8, Folder 8)
  negatives
- G.E.B. Meeting 1989 Palm Springs (Box 8, Folder 9)
  90 photographs
- G.E.B. Meeting - 1991 - Palm Springs (Box 8, Folder 10)
  116 photographs
- G.E.B. Meeting - 1991 - Palm Springs (Box 8, Folder 11)
  161 photographs
- G.E.B. Meeting, May 1985, Washington, D.C. (Box 8, Folder 12)
  73 photographs
- G.E.B. Meeting May 1985, Washington, DC (Box 8, Folder 13)
  141 photographs
- GEB Meeting - Vancouver, BC -- August 1999 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Vancouver GEB meeting - August 1999 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- General Executive Meeting 1987 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  Proof sheet; 101 photographs
- General Executive Meeting 1987 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  negatives; 93 photographs
- Georgetown (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Go Kart Race (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Golf Tournament - 1976 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  13 photographs; Proof sheets
- Golf Championship - Miami, FL 1977 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  Proofs; (Frank Alexander Photos); Tip O'Neil reception
- Golf Tournaments, Board Meetings, Jan. 1985 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Grievance Seminar - DC -- Mar. 1986 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Grievance Seminar - DC- March 1986 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Groundbreaking (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Group Shots Misc. (Box 8, Folder 26)
  32 photographs
- GST Report (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Hail to the Cook! (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Hanely Scholars (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Harvard Club Strike (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Health Care (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Health Care (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Health Care with Dignity Festival (Box 8, Folder 33)
  48 photographs
- Hearing (Box 8, Folder 34)
  proof sheets
- HERE - 1991 - Staff (Box 9, Folder 1)
  proof sheets; 5 photographs
- Headquarters Photos (Box 9, Folder 2)
- HERE Headquarters (Box 9, Folder 3)
- HERE Headquarters (Box 9, Folder 4)
- HERE Headquarters (Box 9, Folder 5)
- HERE Headquarters (Box 9, Folder 6)
- HERE Headquarters (Box 9, Folder 7)
- HERE Headquarters (Box 9, Folder 8)
- HERE Headquarters (Box 9, Folder 9)
- HERE Headquarters (Box 9, Folder 10)
- HERE Headquarters (Box 9, Folder 11)
- HERE Headquarters (Box 9, Folder 12)
- HERE Headquarters (Box 9, Folder 13)
  2 photographs; proof sheets; negatives
- HERE Vice President (Box 9, Folder 14)
  36 photographs; proof sheets
- Hotels (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Ambassador Hotel Employees (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Hotel - Bel Air (Box 9, Folder 17)
  4 slides
- Bellagio Water show (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Hotel - Century Plaza (Box 9, Folder 19)
  7 photographs; 8 slides
- Chicago Hilton (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Concord Hilton Hotel Employees (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Hotel - Disneyland (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Drake Hotel Employees (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Hotel - 4 Queens (Box 9, Folder 24)
  16 photographs; negatives
- Frontier (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Frontier Rally - LIUNA (Box 9, Folder 26)
  25 photographs; negatives; proof sheets
- Hilton Plaza (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Hyatt (Box 9, Folder 28)
  34 photographs; negatives
- Mayflower (Box 9, Folder 29)
  8 photographs; negatives
- Mayflower, Fred Hawerill (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Mayflower, Hotel Washington Kitchen, Food and Bed (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Hotels - Misc. (Box 9, Folder 32)
  55 photographs
- Hotels - New York (Box 9, Folder 33)
  5 photographs; negatives
- Sheraton - Newark - (NYS) (Box 9, Folder 34)
- Shoreham (Box 9, Folder 35)
- Shoreham (Box 9, Folder 36)
  27 photographs; negatives
- Shoreham (Box 9, Folder 37)
  26 photographs; negative
- Shoreham (Box 9, Folder 38)
- Hotel - Westin (Box 9, Folder 39)
- Hotel Employees (Box 9, Folder 40)
  57 photographs
- Hotel Employees at work (Box 9, Folder 41)
  32 photographs; negatives
- Hotel Employees (Box 9, Folder 42)
  38 photographs; negatives
- Hotel Employees - Vista (Box 9, Folder 43)
- Hotel Washing - HSK/Laundry (Box 9, Folder 44)
- Hotel Employees - Kitchen (Box 9, Folder 45)
  21 Hotel Employees - Vista
- Houses (Box 9, Folder 46)
- Hurricane Hugo (Box 9, Folder 47)
- I.L.O. (Box 9, Folder 48)
- I.L.P.A. (Box 9, Folder 49)
- Management Workers Rally (Box 9, Folder 50)
  47 photographs; proof sheets; negatives
- Individuals (Box 9, Folder 51)
- Individuals (Box 9, Folder 52)
- Individuals - Misc. (Box 9, Folder 53)
- Unidentified individuals (Box 9, Folder 54)
- Individuals (slides) (Box 9, Folder 55)
  34 slides; 1 photograph
- Industry training Program o New York Hotel an d Motel Trades Council and Hotel Assn. of NY (Box 9, Folder 56)
- Installation of Officers (Box 9, Folder 57)
- Installation of Officers and Executive Board - Local 224 - 6/1/2001 (Box 9, Folder 58)
- International (Box 9, Folder 59)
- I.T.F. Delegates (Box 9, Folder 60)
- I.U.D. AFL-CIO (Box 9, Folder 61)
- IU Staff 1996 May (Box 9, Folder 62)
  152 slides
- Irish - October 1998 (Box 9, Folder 63)
- Irish, October, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 64)
- Japanese Union (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Jaworski Holiday Inn Protest (Box 10, Folder 2)
- J.E.B. Albuquerque, NM (Box 10, Folder 3)
- J.E.B. Anchorage, Alaska (Box 10, Folder 4)
- J.E.B. Boston, MA (ceased to exist 7-31-1976) (Box 10, Folder 5)
- J.E.B. Buffalo, NY (ceased to exist) (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Joint Executive Board - Butte, Mont. (Box 10, Folder 7)
- J.E.B. Chicago, Ill. (Box 10, Folder 8)
- J.E.B. Chicago - Installation May 1960 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- J.E.B. Cincinnati, OH (Box 10, Folder 10)
- J.E.B. Cleveland, OH (Box 10, Folder 11)
- J.E.B. Denver, CO (Box 10, Folder 12)
- J.E.B. Duluth, Minn. (Box 10, Folder 13)
- J.E.B. Hoboken, NJ (Box 10, Folder 14)
- J.E.B. Kansas City, MO (Box 10, Folder 15)
- J.E.B. Las Vegas, NV (Box 10, Folder 16)
- J.E.B. Long Beach, CA (Box 10, Folder 17)
- J.E.B. Los Angeles (training) 1954 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- J.E.B. Los Angeles (ceased to exist June 30, 1976) -- 8/21/1976 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  59 photographs
- J.E.B. Los Angeles, CA May 1971 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- J.E.B. Minneapolis, Minn. (Box 10, Folder 21)
- J.E.B. New York, NY (Box 10, Folder 22)
- J.E. B. Philadelphia, PA (Box 10, Folder 23)
- J.E.B. Portland, OR (ceased 11-30-1986) (Box 10, Folder 24)